{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562045275","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562045275"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 58ca4d56-79af-4058-9fbf-4f5757cffe91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_23_1-13-23"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 23"," userResponse":" 23"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562051882","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562051881"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 58ca4d56-79af-4058-9fbf-4f5757cffe91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_15_9-5-15"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 15"," userResponse":" 15"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562058703","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562058703"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 58ca4d56-79af-4058-9fbf-4f5757cffe91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_24_24-1-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 24"," userResponse":" 24"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562064353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562064353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 58ca4d56-79af-4058-9fbf-4f5757cffe91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_21_0-1-21"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 21"," userResponse":" 21"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562070295","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562070294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 58ca4d56-79af-4058-9fbf-4f5757cffe91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-8-6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 16"," userResponse":" 16"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562076467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562076467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 58ca4d56-79af-4058-9fbf-4f5757cffe91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-10-12"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 16"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562082816","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562082816"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 58ca4d56-79af-4058-9fbf-4f5757cffe91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-10-12"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 16"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562088779","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562088779"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 58ca4d56-79af-4058-9fbf-4f5757cffe91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-10-12"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 16"," userResponse":" 16"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562095448","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562095448"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 58ca4d56-79af-4058-9fbf-4f5757cffe91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_23_12-4-23"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 23"," userResponse":" 23"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562102083","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562102083"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 58ca4d56-79af-4058-9fbf-4f5757cffe91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_18_9-18-6"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 18"," userResponse":" 18"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562108325","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562108325"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 58ca4d56-79af-4058-9fbf-4f5757cffe91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_23_4-6-23"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 23"," userResponse":" 23"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562113719","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562113719"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 58ca4d56-79af-4058-9fbf-4f5757cffe91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_20_1-20-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 20"," userResponse":" 20"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562121106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562121106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 58ca4d56-79af-4058-9fbf-4f5757cffe91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_20_1-20-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562334925","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562334923"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 58ca4d56-79af-4058-9fbf-4f5757cffe91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_20_1-20-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562335024","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562335024"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 6a3fb2d7-4915-45ed-abe2-753dd5a52726"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kutoka siku hiyo walikuwa maadui!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAADUI"," userResponse":" MAADUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562344285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562344285"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2c1fc5c8-73fc-476c-ae59-5a5a9f510d6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562345359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562345358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2c1fc5c8-73fc-476c-ae59-5a5a9f510d6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562346047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562346047"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2c1fc5c8-73fc-476c-ae59-5a5a9f510d6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562346140","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562346140"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2c1fc5c8-73fc-476c-ae59-5a5a9f510d6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562351518","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562351517"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2c1fc5c8-73fc-476c-ae59-5a5a9f510d6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562360020","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562360020"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562363455","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562363455"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562366858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562366858"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562370858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562370858"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562374191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562374191"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562377859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562377858"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562384525","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562384525"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562389178","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562389178"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562394234","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562394233"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562400086","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562400086"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562404697","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562404697"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562410002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562410002"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562415461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562415461"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562419600","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562419600"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562423516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562423516"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562426396","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562426396"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562435360","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562435360"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562438882","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562438882"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562442439","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562442439"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-J-F"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562445952","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562445952"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562448883","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562448883"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-U-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562451652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562451652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562454548","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562454548"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562457875","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562457875"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562463642","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562463641"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562758887","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562758886"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 821c9f5b-2c57-4105-aa21-1d9c6f823b55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562758947","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562758946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 32c56f15-b212-4928-8d3f-fa94386f6a97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwaheri!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAHERI"," userResponse":" KWAHERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562767453","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562767452"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e6d92e8a-98a9-45ff-b351-2e8aeac5d01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.71"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_P-Y-F"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562771024","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562771023"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e6d92e8a-98a9-45ff-b351-2e8aeac5d01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.71"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_R-Y-H"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562795346","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562795346"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e6d92e8a-98a9-45ff-b351-2e8aeac5d01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.71"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_H-G-Y"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562807662","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562807662"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e6d92e8a-98a9-45ff-b351-2e8aeac5d01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.71"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Z-S-Y"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562811356","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562811356"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e6d92e8a-98a9-45ff-b351-2e8aeac5d01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.71"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_I-F-Y"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562820074","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562820073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e6d92e8a-98a9-45ff-b351-2e8aeac5d01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.71"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-D-W"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562828095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562828095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e6d92e8a-98a9-45ff-b351-2e8aeac5d01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.71"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-T-Y"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562831944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562831944"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e6d92e8a-98a9-45ff-b351-2e8aeac5d01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.71"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_S-F-Y"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562835741","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562835741"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e6d92e8a-98a9-45ff-b351-2e8aeac5d01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.71"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_P-Y-M"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562840061","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562840061"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e6d92e8a-98a9-45ff-b351-2e8aeac5d01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.71"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-Z-A"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562845791","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562845790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e6d92e8a-98a9-45ff-b351-2e8aeac5d01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.show.71"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-Z-A"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562862505","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562862505"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 309f834f-0b03-4827-abf0-c418662b3c0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_23_1-13-23"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 23"," userResponse":" 23"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562868188","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562868188"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 309f834f-0b03-4827-abf0-c418662b3c0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_15_9-5-15"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 15"," userResponse":" 15"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562874841","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562874841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 309f834f-0b03-4827-abf0-c418662b3c0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_18_9-18-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 18"," userResponse":" 18"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562879950","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562879950"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 309f834f-0b03-4827-abf0-c418662b3c0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_20_1-20-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 20"," userResponse":" 20"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562885540","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562885540"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 309f834f-0b03-4827-abf0-c418662b3c0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_21_0-1-21"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 21"," userResponse":" 21"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562891447","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562891447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 309f834f-0b03-4827-abf0-c418662b3c0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_23_4-6-23"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 23"," userResponse":" 23"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562898863","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562898863"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 309f834f-0b03-4827-abf0-c418662b3c0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_23_12-4-23"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 23"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562910194","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562910194"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 309f834f-0b03-4827-abf0-c418662b3c0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_23_12-4-23"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 23"," userResponse":" 23"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562916049","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562916049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 309f834f-0b03-4827-abf0-c418662b3c0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_24_24-1-2"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 24"," userResponse":" 24"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562923980","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562923979"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 309f834f-0b03-4827-abf0-c418662b3c0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-10-12"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 16"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562932593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562932593"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 309f834f-0b03-4827-abf0-c418662b3c0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-10-12"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 16"," userResponse":" 16"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562937969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562937969"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 309f834f-0b03-4827-abf0-c418662b3c0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-8-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 16"," userResponse":" 16"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562944994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562944992"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 309f834f-0b03-4827-abf0-c418662b3c0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-8-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562953236","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562953236"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0971b2f-73db-44e5-85fc-49ca6dc4fa7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_S-M-Y"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562956262","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562956262"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0971b2f-73db-44e5-85fc-49ca6dc4fa7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-S-P"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562959450","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562959449"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0971b2f-73db-44e5-85fc-49ca6dc4fa7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Z-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562963309","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562963309"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0971b2f-73db-44e5-85fc-49ca6dc4fa7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_O-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562967482","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562967482"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0971b2f-73db-44e5-85fc-49ca6dc4fa7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_U-Y-K"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562970765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562970764"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0971b2f-73db-44e5-85fc-49ca6dc4fa7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_I-Y-O"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562975170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562975170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0971b2f-73db-44e5-85fc-49ca6dc4fa7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-J-M"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562978891","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562978890"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0971b2f-73db-44e5-85fc-49ca6dc4fa7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-U-S"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562982432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562982432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0971b2f-73db-44e5-85fc-49ca6dc4fa7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_K-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562986137","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562986137"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0971b2f-73db-44e5-85fc-49ca6dc4fa7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_J-Y-U"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548562991862","data":{"timestamp":" 1548562991862"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0971b2f-73db-44e5-85fc-49ca6dc4fa7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_J-Y-U"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563000812","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563000811"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0971b2f-73db-44e5-85fc-49ca6dc4fa7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_J-Y-U"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563008031","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563008030"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0971b2f-73db-44e5-85fc-49ca6dc4fa7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_J-Y-U"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563020443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563020443"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 08d52429-15ee-4c6c-be68-44e93fff6af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-12-13"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 16"," userResponse":" 13"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563026651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563026651"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 08d52429-15ee-4c6c-be68-44e93fff6af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-12-13"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 16"," userResponse":" 16"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563031879","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563031879"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 08d52429-15ee-4c6c-be68-44e93fff6af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_1-10-11"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563036832","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563036832"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 08d52429-15ee-4c6c-be68-44e93fff6af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-10-3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 16"," userResponse":" 16"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563042274","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563042274"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 08d52429-15ee-4c6c-be68-44e93fff6af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_11-12-13"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 13"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563049394","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563049394"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 08d52429-15ee-4c6c-be68-44e93fff6af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_11-12-13"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563054903","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563054903"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 08d52429-15ee-4c6c-be68-44e93fff6af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_15_8-7-15"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 15"," userResponse":" 15"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563059806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563059806"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 08d52429-15ee-4c6c-be68-44e93fff6af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_15_11-7-15"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 15"," userResponse":" 15"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563065350","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563065350"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 08d52429-15ee-4c6c-be68-44e93fff6af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_14_8-4-14"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 14"," userResponse":" 14"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563070184","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563070184"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 08d52429-15ee-4c6c-be68-44e93fff6af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_2-10-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563074888","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563074888"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 08d52429-15ee-4c6c-be68-44e93fff6af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_17_17-3-5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 17"," userResponse":" 17"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563080879","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563080878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 08d52429-15ee-4c6c-be68-44e93fff6af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_14_8-9-14"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 14"," userResponse":" 14"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563087869","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563087867"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 08d52429-15ee-4c6c-be68-44e93fff6af8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_14_8-9-14"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563097284","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563097284"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563100043","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563100043"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563103268","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563103267"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563106662","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563106662"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563110296","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563110296"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563114591","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563114591"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563117669","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563117669"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563128335","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563128335"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563132219","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563132219"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563135416","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563135416"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563138650","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563138650"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563141712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563141712"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563145320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563145320"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563150925","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563150924"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563153933","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563153933"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563157080","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563157080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563160073","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563160073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563163329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563163329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563166529","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563166529"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563169650","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563169650"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563172427","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563172427"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563175385","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563175385"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563178519","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563178518"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563181593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563181593"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563184817","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563184816"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563190564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563190563"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563203116","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563203116"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 7c7f07c2-a649-414a-9a52-bf0df3c9e89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563229203","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563229203"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563230266","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563230265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563232798","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563232798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563233854","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563233854"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563236419","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563236419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563236501","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563236501"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563237489","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563237489"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563239628","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563239628"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563241872","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563241872"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563241918","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563241918"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563243040","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563243040"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563245964","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563245964"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563249923","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563249923"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563250974","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563250974"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563254966","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563254965"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563256001","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563256001"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563257412","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563257412"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563258448","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563258448"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563261585","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563261585"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563262628","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563262628"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563265899","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563265899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563266942","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563266942"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563270264","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563270263"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563271323","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563271323"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563279334","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563279334"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563280398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563280398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563284166","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563284165"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563285206","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563285206"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563288093","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563288093"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563288320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563288320"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563289206","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563289206"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563291717","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563291717"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563296127","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563296127"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" START_T"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563297180","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563297179"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563298236","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563298236"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563303467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563303467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563304518","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563304518"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563306960","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563306960"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563307992","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563307992"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563312895","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563312895"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563313975","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563313975"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563317652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563317651"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563318713","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563318712"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563321645","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563321644"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563322722","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563322722"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563326099","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563326098"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563326199","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563326199"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..29.off2.19__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563347572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563347572"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 1dae5bb0-55c5-46c8-bf05-bf5821867f8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563380937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563380937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 6f7a50cb-90d2-4d5e-994c-373fc38d9008"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563389308","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563389308"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 6f7a50cb-90d2-4d5e-994c-373fc38d9008"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563392583","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563392583"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 6f7a50cb-90d2-4d5e-994c-373fc38d9008"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563396219","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563396219"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 6f7a50cb-90d2-4d5e-994c-373fc38d9008"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563402427","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563402427"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 6f7a50cb-90d2-4d5e-994c-373fc38d9008"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563405901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563405901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 6f7a50cb-90d2-4d5e-994c-373fc38d9008"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563409470","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563409470"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 6f7a50cb-90d2-4d5e-994c-373fc38d9008"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563412831","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563412831"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 6f7a50cb-90d2-4d5e-994c-373fc38d9008"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563416536","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563416535"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 6f7a50cb-90d2-4d5e-994c-373fc38d9008"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563420730","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563420730"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 6f7a50cb-90d2-4d5e-994c-373fc38d9008"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563423682","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563423682"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 6f7a50cb-90d2-4d5e-994c-373fc38d9008"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563429503","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563429503"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 6f7a50cb-90d2-4d5e-994c-373fc38d9008"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563523538","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563523537"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 6f7a50cb-90d2-4d5e-994c-373fc38d9008"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563526342","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563526341"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 6f7a50cb-90d2-4d5e-994c-373fc38d9008"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563531511","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563531511"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 6f7a50cb-90d2-4d5e-994c-373fc38d9008"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563553212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563553212"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 95e0115c-2155-49cb-b2c7-de26a12fbf40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Z-K-W"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563556728","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563556727"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 95e0115c-2155-49cb-b2c7-de26a12fbf40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Y-E-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563559491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563559490"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 95e0115c-2155-49cb-b2c7-de26a12fbf40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Z-W-A"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563562228","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563562228"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 95e0115c-2155-49cb-b2c7-de26a12fbf40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Z-O-I"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563564844","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563564844"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 95e0115c-2155-49cb-b2c7-de26a12fbf40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Z-A-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563567950","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563567950"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 95e0115c-2155-49cb-b2c7-de26a12fbf40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_E-Z-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563570979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563570979"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 95e0115c-2155-49cb-b2c7-de26a12fbf40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_V-A-Z"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563574086","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563574085"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 95e0115c-2155-49cb-b2c7-de26a12fbf40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_D-Y-Z"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563576965","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563576965"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 95e0115c-2155-49cb-b2c7-de26a12fbf40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Z-CH-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563583050","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563583050"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 95e0115c-2155-49cb-b2c7-de26a12fbf40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_F-Z-K"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563588827","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563588827"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 95e0115c-2155-49cb-b2c7-de26a12fbf40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_F-Z-K"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563594564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563594563"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 95e0115c-2155-49cb-b2c7-de26a12fbf40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_F-Z-K"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563608777","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563608777"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" ca926383-b212-43ea-9cb9-f41074ad61ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_D-Y-Z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563616275","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563616275"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" ca926383-b212-43ea-9cb9-f41074ad61ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_V-A-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563624708","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563624708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" ca926383-b212-43ea-9cb9-f41074ad61ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Y-E-Z"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563647132","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563647131"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" ca926383-b212-43ea-9cb9-f41074ad61ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_E-Z-H"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563651242","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563651241"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" ca926383-b212-43ea-9cb9-f41074ad61ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Z-CH-K"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563659700","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563659700"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" ca926383-b212-43ea-9cb9-f41074ad61ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Z-A-E"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563675657","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563675657"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" ca926383-b212-43ea-9cb9-f41074ad61ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Z-K-W"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563702955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563702955"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" ca926383-b212-43ea-9cb9-f41074ad61ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Z-W-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563705932","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563705932"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" ca926383-b212-43ea-9cb9-f41074ad61ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Z-O-I"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563710068","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563710068"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" ca926383-b212-43ea-9cb9-f41074ad61ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_F-Z-K"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563715831","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563715829"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" ca926383-b212-43ea-9cb9-f41074ad61ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_F-Z-K"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563729727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563729727"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" ca926383-b212-43ea-9cb9-f41074ad61ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_F-Z-K"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563747325","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563747325"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" d766f7be-7dff-4d97-aaec-e97931ba681e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_L-V-Z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563753027","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563753027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" d766f7be-7dff-4d97-aaec-e97931ba681e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_A-CH-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563756485","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563756485"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" d766f7be-7dff-4d97-aaec-e97931ba681e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_CH-Z-D"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563760241","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563760241"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" d766f7be-7dff-4d97-aaec-e97931ba681e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_H-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563763798","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563763798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" d766f7be-7dff-4d97-aaec-e97931ba681e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_F-K-Z"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563767214","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563767214"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" d766f7be-7dff-4d97-aaec-e97931ba681e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Z-U-F"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563770291","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563770291"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" d766f7be-7dff-4d97-aaec-e97931ba681e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_B-Z-I"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563773138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563773138"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" d766f7be-7dff-4d97-aaec-e97931ba681e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Z-U-W"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563775986","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563775985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" d766f7be-7dff-4d97-aaec-e97931ba681e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Z-Y-A"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563779203","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563779203"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" d766f7be-7dff-4d97-aaec-e97931ba681e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_CH-Z-G"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563784948","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563784946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" d766f7be-7dff-4d97-aaec-e97931ba681e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_CH-Z-G"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563797011","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563797011"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" d766f7be-7dff-4d97-aaec-e97931ba681e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_CH-Z-G"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563824754","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563824754"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e861c7e3-bfbb-4628-b006-18999d008d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563828014","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563828014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e861c7e3-bfbb-4628-b006-18999d008d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563829624","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563829624"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e861c7e3-bfbb-4628-b006-18999d008d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563833557","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563833557"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e861c7e3-bfbb-4628-b006-18999d008d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563835137","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563835136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e861c7e3-bfbb-4628-b006-18999d008d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563837829","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563837829"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e861c7e3-bfbb-4628-b006-18999d008d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563839408","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563839408"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e861c7e3-bfbb-4628-b006-18999d008d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563841421","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563841421"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e861c7e3-bfbb-4628-b006-18999d008d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563843029","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563843029"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e861c7e3-bfbb-4628-b006-18999d008d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563845173","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563845173"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e861c7e3-bfbb-4628-b006-18999d008d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563846827","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563846827"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e861c7e3-bfbb-4628-b006-18999d008d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563849307","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563849307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e861c7e3-bfbb-4628-b006-18999d008d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563850870","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563850870"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e861c7e3-bfbb-4628-b006-18999d008d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563853060","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563853060"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e861c7e3-bfbb-4628-b006-18999d008d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563854653","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563854653"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e861c7e3-bfbb-4628-b006-18999d008d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563856758","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563856758"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e861c7e3-bfbb-4628-b006-18999d008d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563858382","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563858382"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e861c7e3-bfbb-4628-b006-18999d008d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563859658","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563859657"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e861c7e3-bfbb-4628-b006-18999d008d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563859757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563859757"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e861c7e3-bfbb-4628-b006-18999d008d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..29.off2.19__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563865467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563865467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" e861c7e3-bfbb-4628-b006-18999d008d06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563880605","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563880605"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563881650","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563881650"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563884010","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563884010"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563884212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563884212"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563885095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563885095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563887490","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563887489"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563889949","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563889949"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563890002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563890002"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563891077","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563891076"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563893332","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563893332"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563895763","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563895763"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563895881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563895881"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563896878","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563896878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563899083","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563899083"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563901681","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563901681"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563903318","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563903318"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563905908","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563905907"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563906947","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563906947"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563910080","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563910080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563911123","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563911123"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563912415","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563912415"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563912621","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563912621"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563913509","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563913509"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563915966","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563915966"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563918747","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563918747"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563918895","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563918895"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563919853","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563919853"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563922178","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563922178"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563924745","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563924745"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563926389","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563926389"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563929179","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563929178"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563930225","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563930225"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563933148","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563933148"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563933623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563933622"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563934343","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563934343"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563936845","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563936845"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563939579","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563939579"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563941229","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563941229"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563943965","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563943964"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563945603","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563945603"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563948208","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563948208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563949258","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563949257"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563952015","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563952014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563953808","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563953808"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563956322","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563956321"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563957967","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563957967"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563960595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563960595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563960694","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563960694"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563962717","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563962717"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563962859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563962859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 2e9e46fa-5437-4a47-8643-61641facc2ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563972712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563972712"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563972955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563972955"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563973852","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563973850"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563974354","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563974354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563974938","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563974936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYUMBA"," userResponse":" VYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563975851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563975851"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" VIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563976988","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563976988"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563977880","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563977880"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAANZA"," userResponse":" WANAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563978712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563978711"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKUWA"," userResponse":" KUTOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563978995","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563978995"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563979791","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563979791"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563982433","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563982432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563982632","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563982632"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563983480","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563983480"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWITUNI"," userResponse":" MWITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563984336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563984336"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" WALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563985011","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563985010"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFIKA"," userResponse":" KUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563985647","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563985646"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563986229","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563986229"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563987549","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563987549"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAOGOFYA"," userResponse":" KUWAOGOFYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563990824","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563990824"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563991295","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563991294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563992164","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563992163"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKULA"," userResponse":" WALIKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563992837","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563992837"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMEA"," userResponse":" MIMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563993393","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563993392"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563993962","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563993961"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563996436","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563996436"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563997632","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563997632"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWABEBA"," userResponse":" WALIWABEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563998666","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563998666"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548563998890","data":{"timestamp":" 1548563998890"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564000006","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564000006"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAONDOSHA"," userResponse":" KUWAONDOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564000400","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564000400"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564003432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564003432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAPAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564004131","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564004130"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAHALI"," userResponse":" PAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564004917","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564004917"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAZURI"," userResponse":" PAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564005135","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564005134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PA"," userResponse":" PA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564005858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564005858"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564006482","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564006482"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564009120","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564009119"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564009912","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564009912"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGEENDA"," userResponse":" WANGEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564010836","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564010835"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564013969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564013969"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564014543","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564014543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564015477","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564015477"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPATA"," userResponse":" ILIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564016051","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564016051"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIBU"," userResponse":" JIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564019246","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564019246"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIKUWA"," userResponse":" HAIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564020010","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564020010"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIGUMU"," userResponse":" VIGUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564020716","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564020716"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPATA"," userResponse":" KUPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564021533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564021533"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564022712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564022711"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564025713","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564025713"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHAKA"," userResponse":" VICHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564026616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564026616"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIMEA"," userResponse":" VILIMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564027692","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564027692"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564028015","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564028014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564028655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564028654"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENGO"," userResponse":" PENGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564028910","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564028909"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564029695","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564029694"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAMBA"," userResponse":" MIAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564032225","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564032225"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564033028","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564033028"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIMEA"," userResponse":" ILIMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564033522","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564033522"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564034697","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564034697"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITELEMKO"," userResponse":" MITELEMKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564034931","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564034931"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564035741","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564035740"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMA"," userResponse":" MILIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564038497","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564038497"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi walitega sungura wa miambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564039551","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564039551"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi walitega sungura wa miambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITEGA"," userResponse":" WALITEGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564040446","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564040446"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi walitega sungura wa miambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564040600","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564040600"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi walitega sungura wa miambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564041623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564041623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi walitega sungura wa miambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAMBANI"," userResponse":" MIAMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564044553","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564044553"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walishika ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564045567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564045567"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walishika ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISHIKA"," userResponse":" WALISHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564046160","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564046160"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walishika ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564049362","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564049361"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564050297","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564050296"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINGINE"," userResponse":" ZINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564051660","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564051660"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIONA"," userResponse":" ZILIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564052263","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564052263"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINSI"," userResponse":" JINSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564053040","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564053039"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564053284","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564053284"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564054168","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564054168"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564055153","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564055153"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIVYOISHI"," userResponse":" ILIVYOISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564056318","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564056318"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIZURI"," userResponse":" VIZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564058899","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564058899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" MAISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564059112","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564059112"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564059596","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564059595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULE"," userResponse":" KULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564060450","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564060449"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564060654","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564060654"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564061738","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564061737"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZURI"," userResponse":" MAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564062604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564062604"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564063558","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564063558"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564066317","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564066317"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564066842","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564066842"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJE"," userResponse":" MJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564067356","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564067356"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKO"," userResponse":" HUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564067890","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564067890"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564070759","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564070759"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo punde familia zingine zilihamia milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564071552","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564071552"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo punde familia zingine zilihamia milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDE"," userResponse":" PUNDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564072516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564072516"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo punde familia zingine zilihamia milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564073290","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564073290"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo punde familia zingine zilihamia milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINGINE"," userResponse":" ZINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564074425","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564074424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo punde familia zingine zilihamia milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIHAMIA"," userResponse":" ZILIHAMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564075469","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564075468"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo punde familia zingine zilihamia milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564077916","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564077916"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564078829","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564078829"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564079773","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564079773"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPATA"," userResponse":" ILIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564080348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564080348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANGO"," userResponse":" PANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564081032","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564081032"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564081796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564081796"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564082609","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564082609"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564083094","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564083094"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564084064","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564084064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAPATA"," userResponse":" WAKAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564084937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564084937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564085109","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564085109"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564085563","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564085562"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564086457","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564086457"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila familia ilipata pango na kuishi ndani na wakapata joto na kuwa salama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SALAMA"," userResponse":" SALAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564089440","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564089439"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde watoto walikuwa wepesi wa kupanda miamba na kutafuta matunda mitini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDE"," userResponse":" PUNDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564090283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564090283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde watoto walikuwa wepesi wa kupanda miamba na kutafuta matunda mitini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564091152","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564091151"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde watoto walikuwa wepesi wa kupanda miamba na kutafuta matunda mitini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564092208","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564092207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde watoto walikuwa wepesi wa kupanda miamba na kutafuta matunda mitini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEPESI"," userResponse":" WEPESI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564092759","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564092758"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde watoto walikuwa wepesi wa kupanda miamba na kutafuta matunda mitini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564093447","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564093447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde watoto walikuwa wepesi wa kupanda miamba na kutafuta matunda mitini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" KUPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564094365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564094364"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde watoto walikuwa wepesi wa kupanda miamba na kutafuta matunda mitini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAMBA"," userResponse":" MIAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564095013","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564095013"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde watoto walikuwa wepesi wa kupanda miamba na kutafuta matunda mitini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564095936","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564095936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde watoto walikuwa wepesi wa kupanda miamba na kutafuta matunda mitini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564096761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564096761"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde watoto walikuwa wepesi wa kupanda miamba na kutafuta matunda mitini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564097607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564097607"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde watoto walikuwa wepesi wa kupanda miamba na kutafuta matunda mitini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITINI"," userResponse":" MITINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564101216","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564101216"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wangening'inia kwenye matawi kama vile kima hufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGENING"," userResponse":" WANGENING"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564101225","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564101225"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wangening'inia kwenye matawi kama vile kima hufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INIA"," userResponse":" INIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564101819","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564101819"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wangening'inia kwenye matawi kama vile kima hufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564102694","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564102694"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wangening'inia kwenye matawi kama vile kima hufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAWI"," userResponse":" MATAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564103158","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564103158"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wangening'inia kwenye matawi kama vile kima hufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564103671","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564103671"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wangening'inia kwenye matawi kama vile kima hufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564104245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564104245"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wangening'inia kwenye matawi kama vile kima hufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564105069","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564105069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wangening'inia kwenye matawi kama vile kima hufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUFANYA"," userResponse":" HUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564108548","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564108548"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Polepole vitu vilianza kubadilika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLEPOLE"," userResponse":" POLEPOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564109502","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564109502"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Polepole vitu vilianza kubadilika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITU"," userResponse":" VITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564110386","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564110386"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Polepole vitu vilianza kubadilika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIANZA"," userResponse":" VILIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564111592","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564111592"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Polepole vitu vilianza kubadilika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBADILIKA"," userResponse":" KUBADILIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564114342","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564114342"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walipunguza kuongea na kukoroma zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564115586","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564115586"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walipunguza kuongea na kukoroma zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPUNGUZA"," userResponse":" WALIPUNGUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564116620","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564116620"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walipunguza kuongea na kukoroma zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONGEA"," userResponse":" KUONGEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564117244","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564117244"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walipunguza kuongea na kukoroma zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564118257","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564118257"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walipunguza kuongea na kukoroma zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOROMA"," userResponse":" KUKOROMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564119041","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564119041"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walipunguza kuongea na kukoroma zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564121429","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564121429"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha watu wazima waliona kwamba pua zao zilikuwa zinakuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564121905","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564121905"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha watu wazima waliona kwamba pua zao zilikuwa zinakuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564122709","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564122709"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha watu wazima waliona kwamba pua zao zilikuwa zinakuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZIMA"," userResponse":" WAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564123633","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564123633"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha watu wazima waliona kwamba pua zao zilikuwa zinakuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" WALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564124277","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564124277"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha watu wazima waliona kwamba pua zao zilikuwa zinakuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564125213","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564125213"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha watu wazima waliona kwamba pua zao zilikuwa zinakuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564125747","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564125747"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha watu wazima waliona kwamba pua zao zilikuwa zinakuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564126661","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564126661"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha watu wazima waliona kwamba pua zao zilikuwa zinakuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ZILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564127565","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564127564"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha watu wazima waliona kwamba pua zao zilikuwa zinakuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINAKUWA"," userResponse":" ZINAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564128510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564128510"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha watu wazima waliona kwamba pua zao zilikuwa zinakuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564131410","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564131409"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliota nywele zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOTA"," userResponse":" WALIOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564131813","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564131813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliota nywele zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564132757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564132757"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliota nywele zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564135728","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564135728"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipoangaliana waliona kwamba meno yao yalikuwa marefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564137691","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564137691"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipoangaliana waliona kwamba meno yao yalikuwa marefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOANGALIANA"," userResponse":" WALIPOANGALIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564139045","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564139045"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipoangaliana waliona kwamba meno yao yalikuwa marefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" WALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564139619","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564139619"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipoangaliana waliona kwamba meno yao yalikuwa marefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564140072","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564140072"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipoangaliana waliona kwamba meno yao yalikuwa marefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564140365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564140365"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipoangaliana waliona kwamba meno yao yalikuwa marefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564141348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564141348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipoangaliana waliona kwamba meno yao yalikuwa marefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIKUWA"," userResponse":" YALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564142231","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564142231"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila walipoangaliana waliona kwamba meno yao yalikuwa marefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAREFU"," userResponse":" MAREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564145424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564145423"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walianza kutembea kwa miguu minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" WALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564146499","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564146499"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walianza kutembea kwa miguu minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564147242","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564147242"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walianza kutembea kwa miguu minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564148106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564148106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walianza kutembea kwa miguu minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564148869","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564148869"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walianza kutembea kwa miguu minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINNE"," userResponse":" MINNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564152423","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564152423"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa viumbe vipya ambavyo hakuna aliyekuwa amewahi kuona pahali pale mbeleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564153348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564153348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa viumbe vipya ambavyo hakuna aliyekuwa amewahi kuona pahali pale mbeleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIUMBE"," userResponse":" VIUMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564154202","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564154202"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa viumbe vipya ambavyo hakuna aliyekuwa amewahi kuona pahali pale mbeleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPYA"," userResponse":" VIPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564155306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564155306"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa viumbe vipya ambavyo hakuna aliyekuwa amewahi kuona pahali pale mbeleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAVYO"," userResponse":" AMBAVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564155436","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564155436"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Walikuwa viumbe vipya ambavyo hakuna aliyekuwa amewahi kuona pahali pale mbeleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564155522","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564155522"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 4f25a371-4d4b-444b-b872-8700b94638a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa viumbe vipya ambavyo hakuna aliyekuwa amewahi kuona pahali pale mbeleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAVYO"," userResponse":" AMBAVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564185307","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564185307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564207360","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564207360"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_B"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564216452","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564216452"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" C"," userResponse":" C"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564220173","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564220173"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564230358","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564230358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564239791","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564239791"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564252258","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564252258"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564259716","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564259716"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564271455","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564271455"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_F"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564283141","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564283141"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_G"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564295550","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564295550"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_H"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564303806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564303805"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_I"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564310429","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564310429"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_I"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564317542","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564317542"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_I"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564327835","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564327835"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564342464","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564342464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564353358","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564353358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564371482","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564371482"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_M"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564384029","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564384029"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_N"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564414966","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564414966"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564425538","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564425538"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_P"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564437057","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564437057"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_R"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564446765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564446765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564456915","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564456915"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564470980","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564470980"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564483698","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564483698"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_V"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564494773","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564494772"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_W"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564507545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564507544"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564517788","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564517788"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564527981","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564527981"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564534448","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564534446"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" f1f89f98-7d90-4042-8e24-de57d4035fb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564543110","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564543110"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564546763","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564546763"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564550452","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564550452"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564553343","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564553343"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564556621","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564556621"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564560294","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564560294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564563943","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564563943"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564567089","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564567088"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564570393","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564570393"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564573628","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564573628"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564577119","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564577119"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564584678","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564584678"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564589989","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564589989"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564594967","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564594967"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564602817","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564602817"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564609726","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564609726"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564612580","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564612580"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564620796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564620796"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564629634","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564629634"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-J-F"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564644077","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564644077"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564647478","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564647478"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-U-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564652327","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564652327"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564655155","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564655155"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564660790","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564660790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564666512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564666512"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 59196d01-f5a0-4f2e-a662-d0b66541ff4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564676865","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564676865"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564678282","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564678282"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAKUMBUKA"," userResponse":" UNAKUMBUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564678817","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564678817"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIO"," userResponse":" MBIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564679231","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564679231"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564679796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564679796"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATI"," userResponse":" KATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564680308","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564680308"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564680893","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564680893"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564681086","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564681086"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564681759","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564681759"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564683774","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564683774"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564684252","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564684251"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564684916","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564684915"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564685980","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564685979"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564686639","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564686639"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYOTE"," userResponse":" YEYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564687192","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564687191"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564687891","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564687891"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIKI"," userResponse":" MILIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564687955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564687955"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564688682","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564688681"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564690061","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564690061"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEWEZA"," userResponse":" ALIYEWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564690905","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564690904"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONGEA"," userResponse":" KUONGEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564691645","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564691644"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564691788","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564691788"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564692337","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564692337"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" JAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564693638","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564693638"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564694133","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564694133"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILA"," userResponse":" ILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564694732","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564694732"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564695348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564695348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIO"," userResponse":" MBIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564695753","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564695753"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564696320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564696319"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564697155","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564697155"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPINZANI"," userResponse":" WAPINZANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564697594","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564697594"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564698220","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564698220"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 22"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564716928","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564716927"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564717032","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564717032"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" c0263181-0278-49dd-a8a2-84637657a31e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 22"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564737899","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564737899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 8b1a84e5-085a-4b02-baa7-eb79bb68b026"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_M_W_K"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564744557","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564744557"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 8b1a84e5-085a-4b02-baa7-eb79bb68b026"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Y_R_CH"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564751217","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564751217"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 8b1a84e5-085a-4b02-baa7-eb79bb68b026"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_D_O"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564757894","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564757894"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 8b1a84e5-085a-4b02-baa7-eb79bb68b026"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_M_H_D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564764544","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564764544"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 8b1a84e5-085a-4b02-baa7-eb79bb68b026"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_U_F_E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564771230","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564771230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 8b1a84e5-085a-4b02-baa7-eb79bb68b026"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Z_J_V"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564775221","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564775221"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 8b1a84e5-085a-4b02-baa7-eb79bb68b026"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_Z_J_V"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564789030","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564789029"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 8b1a84e5-085a-4b02-baa7-eb79bb68b026"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_Z_J_V"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564798858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564798857"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_E-T-Y"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564806270","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564806270"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-K-F"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564815181","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564815181"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-K-F"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564822285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564822285"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-K-F"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564830943","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564830943"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_G-N-Y"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564834341","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564834341"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_G-N-CH"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564837814","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564837814"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_J-A-CH"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564844978","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564844978"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_O-G-S"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564850991","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564850991"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_O-G-S"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564865348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564865348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_M-I-CH"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564889164","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564889164"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_M-I-CH"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564892584","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564892584"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_B-A-L"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564896014","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564896014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_B-R-T"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564899493","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564899492"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_S-D-W"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564902968","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564902968"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_N-D-I"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564907957","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564907957"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-T-K"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564911686","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564911686"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_J-K-Y"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564915470","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564915470"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_J-A-R"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564928080","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564928080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_J-A-R"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564933722","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564933722"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_J-A-R"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564937915","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564937915"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-D-Z"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564941212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564941212"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_I-W-O"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564947116","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564947116"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_I-W-O"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564950509","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564950509"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_P-F-L"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564956403","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564956402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_P-F-L"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564959454","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564959454"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_M-CH-L"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564965905","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564965904"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_M-CH-L"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564971878","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564971877"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_S-P-M"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564985614","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564985614"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_S-P-M"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548564992101","data":{"timestamp":" 1548564992100"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-Z-A"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565010050","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565010050"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-Z-A"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565013838","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565013837"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-B-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565019503","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565019502"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_E-Y-R"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565025588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565025587"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_E-Y-R"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565028798","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565028798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_F-U-S"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565031799","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565031799"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-O-T"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565037613","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565037613"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 675e9ea2-e483-4414-9cc2-bfdaf250c087"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-O-T"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565052043","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565052043"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565053263","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565053263"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPOMALIZA"," userResponse":" NINAPOMALIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565053870","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565053870"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGA"," userResponse":" KUOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565054113","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565054113"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565054564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565054564"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565055318","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565055315"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565056288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565056287"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565059202","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565059201"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILI"," userResponse":" MWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565059743","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565059743"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565060845","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565060842"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJIMAJI"," userResponse":" MAJIMAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565061460","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565061459"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565062192","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565062192"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565063340","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565063340"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565066537","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565066537"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565067480","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565067477"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565067951","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565067951"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565069011","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565069011"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565071765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565071765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565072750","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565072750"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565076621","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565076621"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565077111","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565077110"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565077226","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565077226"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565078208","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565078207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565079227","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565079224"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565079973","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565079972"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565080810","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565080810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565081474","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565081471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565083516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565083511"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565083995","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565083994"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDE"," userResponse":" PUNDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565084473","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565084473"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565085350","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565085350"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565085923","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565085923"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565086712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565086712"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565087318","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565087318"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYANYWA"," userResponse":" KUYANYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565090565","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565090565"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565091482","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565091481"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565091998","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565091997"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565093005","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565093005"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565096332","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565096331"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565097438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565097437"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565102057","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565102053"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPAZIA"," userResponse":" MAPAZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565102186","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565102186"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565103226","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565103207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MADIRISHA"," userResponse":" MADIRISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565105002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565105001"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAPAPATIKA"," userResponse":" YANAPAPATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565105620","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565105619"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565106069","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565106068"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565106614","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565106614"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPOLE"," userResponse":" UPOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565108378","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565108368"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANANIPANGUSA"," userResponse":" YANANIPANGUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565108850","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565108850"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USO"," userResponse":" USO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565109394","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565109394"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565112571","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565112571"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565113529","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565113529"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565114042","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565114041"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIKI"," userResponse":" HIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565115135","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565115134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565117855","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565117854"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565118895","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565118892"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565123010","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565123010"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Radi kwa umbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RADI"," userResponse":" RADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565123269","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565123269"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Radi kwa umbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565124266","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565124265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Radi kwa umbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMBALI"," userResponse":" UMBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565127723","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565127722"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWINGU"," userResponse":" MAWINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565128517","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565128516"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEUSI"," userResponse":" MEUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565129761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565129761"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANASONGA"," userResponse":" YANASONGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565130363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565130362"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565130861","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565130860"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565134052","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565134051"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565134930","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565134930"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565135402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565135402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565136412","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565136412"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565139034","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565139034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565140054","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565140054"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565143393","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565143393"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAWI"," userResponse":" MATAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565144818","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565144817"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" YANAWAYAWAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565145307","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565145307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565146037","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565146036"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565147083","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565147083"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTETEMEKA"," userResponse":" KUTETEMEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565150206","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565150206"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565151554","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565151554"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAANGUKA"," userResponse":" YANAANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565151914","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565151914"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565152495","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565152494"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPOLE"," userResponse":" UPOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565155509","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565155508"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya yote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565156506","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565156506"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya yote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFANYA"," userResponse":" ALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565157016","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565157016"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya yote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565159683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565159683"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565160675","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565160675"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565163956","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565163956"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565164151","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565164151"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565164884","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565164883"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565166221","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565166220"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNACHEZA"," userResponse":" TUNACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565167553","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565167553"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565168463","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565168462"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" NAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565169505","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565169504"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUSIA"," userResponse":" KUNUSIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565170799","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565170798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEREMENDE"," userResponse":" PEREMENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565171512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565171512"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAZO"," userResponse":" AMBAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565172042","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565172042"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565173270","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565173270"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATAYARISHA"," userResponse":" ANATAYARISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565175807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565175807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565176730","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565176729"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565177253","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565177252"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIKI"," userResponse":" HIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565178324","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565178323"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565180830","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565180830"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565181832","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565181831"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565185434","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565185433"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILAURI"," userResponse":" BILAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565185937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565185937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYO"," userResponse":" ILIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565186928","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565186928"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHANI"," userResponse":" DIRISHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565188017","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565188017"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAANGUKA"," userResponse":" INAANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565188494","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565188493"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565188700","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565188699"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565189530","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565189530"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHINDO"," userResponse":" KISHINDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565192013","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565192013"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASHUKURU"," userResponse":" NASHUKURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565192609","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565192609"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUNGU"," userResponse":" MUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565193588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565193588"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUWA"," userResponse":" SIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565194232","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565194231"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565196749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565196748"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565197605","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565197605"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFANYA"," userResponse":" ALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565198366","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565198365"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKATILI"," userResponse":" UKATILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565198789","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565198789"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565201182","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565201182"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565201696","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565201696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAKA"," userResponse":" SHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565202700","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565202699"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565202964","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565202964"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565203859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565203859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565207128","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565207128"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Firimbi inapulizwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FIRIMBI"," userResponse":" FIRIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565208273","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565208273"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Firimbi inapulizwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAPULIZWA"," userResponse":" INAPULIZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565210558","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565210558"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565210724","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565210724"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565211350","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565211349"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOSHI"," userResponse":" MOSHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565212284","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565212284"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINAINGIA"," userResponse":" LINAINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565215083","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565215083"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SILIONI"," userResponse":" SILIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565215975","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565215975"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565216567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565216567"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASIKIA"," userResponse":" NASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565216938","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565216938"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIO"," userResponse":" MLIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565217461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565217461"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565219938","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565219938"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565220811","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565220811"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565221275","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565221275"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565222296","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565222295"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565224761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565224761"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565225759","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565225759"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565240194","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565240194"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haionekani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIONEKANI"," userResponse":" HAIONEKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565243407","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565243407"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haisikiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAISIKIKI"," userResponse":" HAISIKIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565246014","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565246014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAFANYA"," userResponse":" INAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565246410","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565246410"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565247017","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565247016"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565247781","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565247780"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565248236","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565248236"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565250747","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565250747"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaweza kuwa nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWEZA"," userResponse":" ANAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565251174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565251174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaweza kuwa nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565251978","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565251978"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaweza kuwa nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565254523","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565254523"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565255267","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565255267"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAKA"," userResponse":" SHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565257414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565257414"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565258157","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565258157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565308085","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565308070"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565308198","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565308198"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 9540dde3-a705-4325-9166-bd2ff272c8ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565316963","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565316963"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 77f21728-aac1-4df2-8395-2592839b589f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_M-CH-L"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565320246","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565320246"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 77f21728-aac1-4df2-8395-2592839b589f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_I-W-O"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565323285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565323284"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 77f21728-aac1-4df2-8395-2592839b589f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-B-Y"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565326751","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565326751"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 77f21728-aac1-4df2-8395-2592839b589f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_J-A-CH"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565332426","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565332426"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 77f21728-aac1-4df2-8395-2592839b589f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_J-A-CH"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565338037","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565338037"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 77f21728-aac1-4df2-8395-2592839b589f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_E-T-Y"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565345414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565345414"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 77f21728-aac1-4df2-8395-2592839b589f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_E-T-Y"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565349063","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565349062"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 77f21728-aac1-4df2-8395-2592839b589f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_J-K-Y"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565352543","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565352543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 77f21728-aac1-4df2-8395-2592839b589f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_F-U-S"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565355658","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565355655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_070709"," gameId":" 77f21728-aac1-4df2-8395-2592839b589f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_U_F-U-S"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}